Archival Collective Bargaining Agreements File 6030
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Auto, Aero, Agri Implement Workers of America; United (UAW) Agreements A-B, 2000-2004 (Box 251, Folder 7)
- Auto Aero, Agri Implement Workers of America; United (UAW) Agreements C, 1993 (Box 251, Folder 9)
- Auto, Aero, Agri Implements Workers of America; United (UAW) Agreements D-E, 1995-2000 (Box 251, Folder 10)
- Auto, Aero, Agri Implement Workers of America; United (UAW), 1993-1999 (Box 252, Folder 1)
- Auto, Aero, Agri Implement Workers of America United (UAW) Agreements G, 2003-2004 (Box 252, Folder 2)
- Auto Aero, Agri Implement Workers of America; United (UAW), 1995-1997 (Box 252, Folder 3)
- Auto, Aero, Agri Implement Workers of America; United (UAW). Agreements M, 1995-1996 (Box 252, Folder 4)
- Auto, Aero, Agri, Implement Workers of America; United (UAW) Agreements N-O, 1998 (Box 252, Folder 5)
- Auto, Aero, Agri Implement Workers of America; United (UAW) Agreements P-Z, 1997-1999 (Box 252, Folder 6)
- Boilermakers, Iron Ship Blacksmith; International. Agreements, 1998 (Box 252, Folder 7)
- Broadcast Employees and Technicians; National Association of Agreements, 1996-2000 (Box 252, Folder 8)
- Chemical Workers Union; International AFL. Agreements, 1993-2000 (Box 252, Folder 9)
- Civil Service Employees Assoc. (CSEA) Agreements, 1995-1999 (Box 252, Folder 10)
- Civil Service Employees Association (AFSCME) Local 855 Agreements, 2003 (Box 252, Folder 11)
- Communication Workers of America Agreements, 1998-2003 (Box 252, Folder 12)
- Corrections Officers' Benevolent Association Agreements, 2003 (Box 252, Folder 13)
- Diesel Workers Union Agreements, 1993-2004 (Box 252, Folder 14)
- Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine and Furniture Workers; International Union of (IUE) Agreements, 1992-2007 (Box 252, Folder 15)
- Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers United (UE) Agreements, 1997-2000 (Box 252, Folder 16)
- Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers United )UE) Agreements, 1997-2000 (Box 252, Folder 17)
- Electrical Workers, Int'l. Brotherhood of (IBEW) Agreements, 1997-2006 (Box 252, Folder 18)
- Electrical Workers; international Brotherhood of (IBEW) Agreements, 2001 (Box 253, Folder 1)
- Elevator Constructors; International Union of Agreements, 2000-2007 (Box 253, Folder 2)
- Food and Commercial Workers; United Agreements, 1994 (Box 253, Folder 3)
- Government Employees, American Federation of Agreements, 1992 (Box 253, Folder 4)
- Letters Carriers, National Association of. Agreements, 1998-2011 (Box 253, Folder 5)
- Locomotive Engineers, Brotherhood of Agreements, 2004 (Box 253, Folder 6)
- Longshoremen's and Warehousemen's Union, 1996-2008 (Box 253, Folder 7)
- Machinists and Aerospace Workers, International Association of Agreements, 2002-2008 (Box 253, Folder 8)
- Machinists; International Association of Agreements, 1994-2001 (Box 253, Folder 9)
- Mine Workers of America, United. Agreements, 2002 (Box 253, Folder 10)
- Musicians, American Federation of Agreements, 2000 (Box 253, Folder 11)
- Office and Professional Employees, International Union of Agreements, 1992-2004 (Box 253, Folder 12)
- Nurses Association Agreements, 1994-1997 (Box 253, Folder 13)
- Office Committee Union Agreements, 1999-2004 (Box 253, Folder 14)
- Oil, Chemical and Atomic Workers, International Union of. Agreements, 1992-1996 (Box 254, Folder 1)
- Pacific Maritime Association Agreements, 2002-2008 (Box 254, Folder 2)
- Paper Workers International Union, United. Agreements, 1994-1996 (Box 254, Folder 3)
- Police Benevolent Association, Inc. Buffalo Agreements, 2003 (Box 254, Folder 4)
- Postal Workers Union, American. Agreements, 2006-2010 (Box 254, Folder 5)
- Railroad Signalmen, Brotherhood of Agreements, 2003 (Box 254, Folder 6)
- Rubber, Cork and Linoleum Workers Agreements, 1994-1997 (Box 254, Folder 7)
- School Bus Service, Inc; National Agreements, 2003 (Box 254, Folder 8)
- Sheet Metal, Air, Rail and Transportation (SMART) Workers Agreements, 2007 (Box 254, Folder 9)
- Sheet Metal Workers' International Association Agreements, 2005 (Box 254, Folder 10)
- State, County and Municipal Employees, Agreements, 1995-1999 (Box 254, Folder 11)
- Steelworkers of America, United. Agreements, 1999 (Box 254, Folder 12)
- Teachers, American Federation of Agreements, 1985-1998 (Box 254, Folder 13)
- Teachers, New York State United Agreements A-F, 1997-2001 (Box 254, Folder 14)
- Teachers, New York State United Agreements G-M, 2002 (Box 254, Folder 15)
- Teachers, New York State United Agreements N-Z, 1995-1999 (Box 254, Folder 16)
- Teamsters, 2008-2013 (Box 255, Folder 1)
- United Transportation Union Brotherhood of Locomotive Engineers, 2001 (Box 255, Folder 2)
- Sidney Typographical Union, 1995-1998 (Box 255, Folder 3)
- University Health Professionals, 1998-2005 (Box 255, Folder 4)
- United University Professionals, 1995-2011 (Box 255, Folder 5)
- Utility Workers Union, 1992-1996 (Box 255, Folder 6)
- Unite 1998-2003 (Box 255, Folder 7)
- Unite, Local 23-25, 2000-2002 (Box 255, Folder 8)
- UNITE, Local 10, 1996 (Box 255, Folder 9)
- UNITE, Local 132-98-102, 2005 (Box 255, Folder 10)
- UNITE 2003-2006 (Box 255, Folder 11)
- UNITE, New England Joint Board, 2003 (Box 255, Folder 12)
- UNITE Southern District Council, 2001-2004 (Box 255, Folder 13)
- UNITE, Local 162, 2000-2003 (Box 255, Folder 14)
- UNITE, Local 1997 (Box 255, Folder 15)
- UNITE, Western States Regional Joint Board (Box 255, Folder 16)
- UNITE and FOUR, 2004 (Box 255, Folder 17)
- UNITE and Office and Professional Employees, Local 153, 2000-2003 (Box 255, Folder 18)
- UNITE - HERE, 2005 (Box 255, Folder 19)
- UNITE, New York - New Jersey Joint Board (Box 255, Folder 20)
- UNITE, Local 155, 1995-1998 (Box 255, Folder 21)
- ILGWU, Local 23-25, 1995 (Box 255, Folder 22)
- Affiliated Dress Manufacturers 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 23)
- Affiliated Dress Manufacturers 2001-2004 (Box 255, Folder 24)
- American Coat, and Suit Manufacturers 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 25)
- American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association 2001-2004 (Box 255, Folder 26)
- Association of Rain Apparel Contractors 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 27)
- Association of Rain Apparel Contractors 2001-2004 (Box 255, Folder 28)
- Greater, Blouse, Skirt and Undergarment Association (Blouse) 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 29)
- Greater Blouse, Skirt and Undergarment Association (Sportswear) 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 30)
- Ladies' Apparel Contractors' Association 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 31)
- Ladies' Apparel Contractors' Association 2001-2004 (Box 255, Folder 32)
- Metropolitan Area Apparel Association 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 33)
- National Association of Blouse Manufacturers 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 34)
- New York Coat and Suit Association 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 35)
- New York Coat and Suit Association 2001-2004 (Box 255, Folder 36)
- New York Raincoat Manufacturers' 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 37)
- New York Raincoat Manufacturers' Association 2001-2004 (Box 255, Folder 38)
- New York Skirt and Sportswear Association 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 39)
- Sportswear Apparel Association 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 40)
- American Cloak and Suit Manufacturers Association 1997-2001 (Box 255, Folder 41)
- Ulster-Greene Arc. 2000-2007 (Box 255, Folder 42)